Guide to the Western Sudan Agricultural Research Project Records 1976-1986
Washington State University Libraries Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections
- Series 2: Records from the Sudan Office
  - WSARP
    - Staffing--Personnel, WSARP Research Project Papers, 1978, 1985 (Box 26, Folder 1000)
    - Staffing--Personnel, Winch Report, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 1001)
    - Staffing--Personnel, Winroch Evaluation, 1986-1987 (Box 26, Folder 1002)
    - Staffing--Personnel, WSARP Stations, Development Study, Drafts (includes final), 1980 (Box 26, Folder 1002.01)
  - Workshops: Ghazala Gawazet, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 1003)
  - Workshops: Ghazala Gawazet, Papers, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 1004)
  - World Bank Report; Statement of Assets, 1981-1982 (Box 26, Folder 1005)
ABBREVIATIONS
ABS Agricultural Bank of Sudan
ADFAED Abu Dhali Fund for Arab Economic Development
AHT Agrar Und Hydrotechnik Gmbch (West Germany)
CID Consortium for International Development
CIMMYT Centro Internacional De Mejoramiento De Maiz Y Trigo
EDF European Development Fund
FAO Food and Agriculture Organization of the United Nations
GAC Gum Arabic Company
GTC West German Agency for Technical Cooperation
HIID Harvard Institute for International Development
HTS Hunting Institute for International Development
IADS International Agricultural Development Service
IBRD International Bank for Reconstruction and Development
IDA International Development Association (World Bank)
ILRAD International Laboratory for Research on Animal Diseases
IRR International Rate of Return
INTSORMIL International Sorghum/Millet Research
INTSOY International Soybean Program
LMMC Livestock and Meat Marketing Commission
MEDD Middle East Development Division
MFC Mechanized Farming Corporation
NDC Nucleas Development Centers (demonstration farms, S. Darfur)
NMAPC Nuba Mountains Agricultural Production Corporation
NMCC Nuba Mountains Cotton Corporation (forerunner of NMAPC)
ODM Overseas Development (Ministry of) U.K.
PAPC Public Agricultural Production Corporation
PPU Provincial Planning Unit
RMR Resource Management and Research, Ltd.
RPU Rural Planning Unit (S. Kordofan)
RWC Rural Water Corporation
SATEC Societe d'Aide Technique at de Cooperation
SFD Saudi Fund for Development
SOC Sudan Oilseeds Company
SSA Soil Survey Administration (Ministry of Agriculture)
ULVA Ultra-Low Volume Atomizer
UNESCO United Nations Education, Scientific, and Cultural Organization
USAID United States Agency for International Development
WSARP Western Sudan Agricultural Research Project